{
    "questions":[
        {
            "question":"What is call order (codes) from most important to least important?",
            "options":[
                "13A, 13B, 14A, 14B, 52, 911, 47",
                "14A, 13A, 14B, 13B, 52, 911, 47",
                "14A, 14B, 13A, 13B, 52, 911, 47",
                "13A, 14A, 13B, 14B, 52, 911, 47"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"Under HIPPAA, with whom can we (as EMS) share information?",
            "options":[
                "EMS, Doctors, Emergency Contacts, PD, Relatives and Caregivers",
                "EMS, Doctors, Emergency Contacts, Relatives and Caregivers", 
                "EMS, Doctors, Emergency Contacts, PD and Caregivers"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"What does the abbreviation 'DRCAB' stand for?",
            "options":[
                "Danger, Response, Circulation, Airway, Breathing",
                "Danger, Risk, Condition, Antibiotics, Biopsy",
                "Diagnosis, Response, Condition, Airway, Biopsy",
                "Diagnosis, Risk, Circulation, Antibiotics, Breathing"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question":"Which radio channel do we (EMS) use to communicate with Doctors?",
            "options":[
                "Channel 2",
                "Channel 6",
                "Channel 9"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"What is used to treat an opioid overdose?",
            "options":[
                "Charcoal Tablets",
                "Epipen (Epinephrine)",
                "Insuline",
                "Narcan"
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"What is used to treat a non opioid overdose?",
            "options":[
                "Epipen (Epinephrine)",
                "Charcoal Tablets",
                "Narcan",
                "Insuline"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"Which 10 code indicates you've \"arrived at the scene\"?",
            "options":[
                "23",
                "47",
                "54",
                "76"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question":"Which 10 code indicates there's an \"injured person\"?",
            "options":[
                "23",
                "47",
                "54",
                "76"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"Which 10 code indicates that there's \"livestock on highway\"?",
            "options":[
                "23",
                "47",
                "54",
                "76"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"Which 10 code indicates you're \"en route\" to a location?",
            "options":[
                "23",
                "47",
                "54",
                "76"
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which (driving) code is corresponds with \"Respond to the call without emergency lights and sirens\"?",
            "options":[
                "Code 1",
                "Code 2",
                "Code 3",
                "Code 4",
                "Code 6"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question":"Which (driving) code is corresponds with \"Respond to the call with emergency lights, but without sirens. (Sirens may be used if necessary, such as to make traffic yield or when going through intersections)\"?",
            "options":[
                "Code 1",
                "Code 2",
                "Code 3",
                "Code 4",
                "Code 6"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"Which (driving) code is corresponds with \"Respond to the call using emergency lights and sirens\"?",
            "options":[
                "Code 1",
                "Code 2",
                "Code 3",
                "Code 4",
                "Code 6"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"Which code is used to signal the \"All clear\"?",
            "options":[
                "Code 1",
                "Code 2",
                "Code 3",
                "Code 4",
                "Code 6"
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which code is used to indicate someone is \"Investigating the area\"?",
            "options":[
                "Code 1",
                "Code 2",
                "Code 3",
                "Code 4",
                "Code 6"
            ],
            "answer": 5
        },
        {
            "question":"When triaging what does the classification \"green\" mean?",
            "options":[
                "Needs hospital care, but is stable. Transport needed.",
                "Stable and walking. No transport required.",
                "A doctor's care is not required. At home treatment and first aid is sufficient. No transport required.",
                "Expectant or deceased. Are treated last if DOA. Transport required."
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"When triaging what does the classification \"yellow\" mean?",
            "options":[
                "Critical. Needs immediate surgery or life-saving intervention. Likely to survive with immediate treatment. Transport needed.",
                "Needs hospital care, but is stable. Transport needed.",
                "Stable and walking. No transport required.",
                "Expectant or deceased. Are treated last if DOA. Transport required."
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"When triaging what does the classification \"red\" mean?",
            "options":[
                "Critical. Needs immediate surgery or life-saving intervention. Likely to survive with immediate treatment. Transport needed.",
                "Needs hospital care, but is stable. Transport needed.",
                "Stable and walking. No transport required.",
                "Expectant or deceased. Are treated last if DOA. Transport required."
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question":"When triaging what does the classification \"white\" mean?",
            "options":[
                "Critical. Needs immediate surgery or life-saving intervention. Likely to survive with immediate treatment. Transport needed.",
                "Needs hospital care, but is stable. Transport needed.",
                "Stable and walking. No transport required.",
                "A doctor's care is not required. At home treatment and first aid is sufficient. No transport required."
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"When triaging what does the classification \"black\" mean?",
            "options":[
                "Critical. Needs immediate surgery or life-saving intervention. Likely to survive with immediate treatment. Transport needed.",
                "Needs hospital care, but is stable. Transport needed.",
                "A doctor's care is not required. At home treatment and first aid is sufficient. No transport required.",
                "Expectant or deceased. Are treated last if DOA. Transport required."
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following medications are you <I><U><B>NOT</B></U></I> allowed to administer as an EMT?",
            "options":[
                "Epinephrine (Increase cardiac output during cardiac arrest)",
                "Morphine (Treats severe pain used with compound fractures / major trauma)",
                "Naloxone (Narcan)(Treats opioid overdose)",
                "Midazolam (Induces sedation, used with seizures)"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following medications are you <I><U><B>NOT</B></U></I> allowed to administer as an EMT?",
            "options":[
                "Insulin (Treats high blood sugar in diabetics)",
                "Epinephrine (Increase cardiac output during cardiac arrest)",
                "Lidocaine (For treating dislocated limbs)",
                "Naloxone (Narcan)(Treats opioid overdose)"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following medications are you <I><U><B>NOT</B></U></I> allowed to administer as an EMT?",
            "options":[
                "Midazolam (Induces sedation, used with seizures)",
                "Insulin (Treats high blood sugar in diabetics)",
                "Epinephrine (Increase cardiac output during cardiac arrest)",
                "Fentanyl (Treat severe pain)"
            ],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"What type of questions would you ask in the case of dizziness / confusion / head injury?",
            "options":[
                "Names of things, What month/year it is, Year of birth",
                "What city they are in, What month/year it is, To name 3 farm animals",
                "Year of birth, Colors of things, To name 3 farm animals",
                "What city they are in, Colors of things, Year of birth"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}